It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
Joining the annual Jipangu Maritial Arts Competition, Musashi keeps winning, changed completely from the previous one.
향례 지팡구 무예 대회에 출전한 무사시는 이전 대회와는 돌변해서 쾌조의 연승을 한다.
But meanwhile, Rikudomaoh, who's looking to take the Three Sacred Treasures from the king,
그러나 그 쯤, 지팡 지배를 꾸미는 육도마왕은 국왕에게서 삼종의 신기를 노려 방패와 곡옥을 빼앗았다.
A Monster!
괴물!
Megaton Castle
메가톤성이오
Mr. Musashi and Otsuru, can you help me?
무사시 씨? 오츠루? 조금 도와줘.
Dear. What are you doing there?
여보. 그런 곳에서 뭐 해?
Shh!
쉿!
Finally, you have semi-finals tomorrow!
내일은 드디어 준결승이구나.
Right-dasu. It's finally time to fight that Kojirō-dasu!
그렇소. 드디어 그 코지로하고 싸울 때가 왔소!
Go for it, Mr. Musashi! I have to work in the store and I can't go cheer for you, but I'm still wishing for your victory!
힘내, 무사시 씨. 난 가게 일이 있으니까 응원하러는 못 가지만 마음속으로는 계속 빌고 있어.
Leave it to me-dasu! I'll win and become the number one Karakuri martial artist of Jipangu!
맡겨두시오! 꼭 이겨서 지팡구 제일의 카라쿠리 무예가가 되어 보이겠소!
And then...
그러면...
And then?
그러면?
And then, Otsuru, as promised, I...
그러면, 오츠루, 약속대로 나도... 그거...
What is it? I can't hear you, Mr. Musashi.
뭐? 잘 안 들려, 무사시 씨.
I'd like to have you as my wife...
내, 내 부인으로...
You already knew-dasu?!
알고 있었소?!
A shooting star!
별똥별!
Wishing Mr. Musashi to win in tomorrow's match.
어떻게든 무사시 씨가 내일 경기에서 이길 수 있도록.
Otsuru...
오츠루...
They won't be needing our cheers, after all!
이래선 우리 응원 따위 필요 없겠는걸?
They're so romantic.
아, 좋겠네.
N- no, not at a place like this! It's embarassing!
어, 어이, 안 돼, 이런 곳에선! 부끄럽게.
Isn't it alright? We're married.
괜찮잖아? 부부인데.
Well, that's true...
아, 그건 그런데...
Dear?
여보?
Akane?
아카네?
Dear!
여보!
What is it?
뭐야?
That's ominous.
불길하군.
No, it's not the time to be watching stars.
안 되지. 별 따위나 바라보고 있을 때가 아니지.
Well. Should this be my finishing pose tomorrow?
좋아, 내일의 결정타 포즈는 이걸로 갈까.
Nah, this looks cool, too...
아니, 그래도 이것도 멋지고...
This is good, too!
오, 이것도 좋네.
(jipangbare: twist of nihonbare; clear and cloudless sky)
(지팡구바레: 니혼바레; 쾌청함)
When the sun rises, the sky of Jipangu is clear and the semi-finals finally begins!
날이 밝으면 지팡구의 하늘에는 구름 한 점 없이 쾌청하다! 드디어 준결승전이 시작된다!
Welcome, 10 million martial art fans! The waiting is soon over!
전국 일천만 무예 팬 여러분! 오래 기다리셨습니다!
The competition on that shining stage is already at semi-finals! Today, we have Senhime as a special guest!
무대를 빛내는 대회도 드디어 준결승! 오늘은 특별 게스트로 방송석에 센히메 님을 모였습니다.
Is this live?!
어, 본방?!
Senhime here! Now looking for a husband! Please contact me!
센히메입니다! 신랑 모집중입니다! 잘 부탁드립니다!
Er, Senhime, who do you think will win?
저, 센히메 님, 오늘의 경기, 누가 이기리라 생각됩니까.
I wonder... I guess the stronger wins and the weaker loses, probably!
그러게... 뭐, 강한 쪽이 이기고 약한 쪽이 지겠지, 분명!
Mr. Musashi. I am truly looking for a match with you.
무사시 님. 이 주베, 대전하게 되기를 진심을 다해 빌겠습니다.
The semi-finals will begin now!
그럼 지금부터 준결승전을 시작하겠습니다.
Red corner: #98 Niten'ichiryū Musashi!
빨강 코너, 98번 이천일류 무사시!
White corner: #99 Ganryu Mister Kojirō!
하양 코너, 99번 간류 미스터 코지로!
-Mr. Kojirō! -Mr. Musashi!
-코지로 님! -무사시 씨!
Even if I win and you lose, or you lose and I win, let's have a good match, Musashi.
내가 이기고 네가 져도, 네가 지고 내가 이겨도 좋은 경기를 하자꾸나, 무사시.
Of course-dasu.
물론이오.
Huh? Even if I win and you lose, or you lose and I win...
어? 내가 이기고 네가 져도, 네가 지고 내가 이겨도...
What was that-dasu?! I lose in both ways-dasu!
뭣이오! 결국 내가 지는 게 아니오!
Tch. You found it out.
칫. 들켰군.
Of course-dasu!
당연하오!
Start!
시작!
Open the door! Open the door!
개문! 개문!
W- what?! Is it true that the certificate of the king, the Three Sacred Treasures have been stolen?
뭐, 뭣이? 그게 정말이오? 국왕의 증표인 삼종의 신기를 빼았겼다는 것이.
Right. They came to invade the palace yesterday night. The sacred sword is safe, though.
그렇습니다. 어젯밤 궁전에 침입해 와서... 어떻게든 성검은 지켰습니다만.
Enemies are in pursuit of us, looking for that.
그걸 노리고 추격자가 뒤따르고 있습니다.
Ieyasu. I'll also ask you to protect the sacred sword from the hands of evil, and recover the stolen treasures.
이에야스. 나도 부탁한다. 악의 손에서 성검을 지키고 빼앗긴 신기를 되찾아 주어라.
Yessir. Just as you instructed. I will gather people fluent in martial arts.
예. 분부대로 하겠습니다. 어서 무예에 뛰어난 자를 모으겠습니다.
I see. The king did ask for a help to Ieyasu.
그런가. 역시 국왕은 이에야스에게 도움을 요청했나.
What will you do, Lord Rikudomaoh. Even if my body became stronger, Edo Castle is impregnable.
어떻게 하시겠습니까, 육도마왕 님. 아무리 제 몸이 강하다고 해도 에도 성은 난공불락의 성.
Hmph. A newcomer like you do not know the true fearfulness of our force!
흥. 너같은 신참은 우리 군의 참된 무서움을 모른다!
What?!
뭐라?!
Stop, Hanzō.
그만해라, 한조.
This is not the time for internal discord.
지금은 동료끼리 싸우고 있을 때가 아니다.
U- understood.
아, 알겠습니다.
Dokuganryu. Prepare for landing.
도쿠간류. 상륙 준비를 해라.
Yessir!
예!
Damn you, you Maoh. You'll regret this.
제기랄. 마왕 놈. 기억해 둬라.
That is awesome! It's a battle full of force!
이건 대단한 상태! 박력 가득한 배틀입니다!
Go for it, Musashi! Hit him! Kojirō, you too!
가라, 무사시! 때려버려! 코지로도 어서!
Do it properly!
똑바로 해!
Got you!
잡았다!
You became better, Musashi. But will you manage to evade my Tsubamegaeshi?
꽤 하게 되었구나, 무사시. 그러나 과연 내 츠바메가에시를 피할 수 있을까?
That's my line-dasu! Niten'ichiryū: Flash Sword!
그건 내가 할 말이오! 이천일류 섬광권!
Stop!
중단!
Who dares to interrupt our match?!
누구냐! 경기를 방해하는 게!
Lord Ieyasu!
이에야스 님!
Grandpa!
할아버지!
Driven by the stress of circumstnaces, the martial arts competition will end here.
사정으로 무예 대회는 여기까지 한다.
No way! Our match is not over-dasu!
그런! 우리 승부 아직 안 났소!
No questions asked! Musashi, Kojirō, follow me with Jūbee.
문답무용이다! 무사시, 코지로, 주베하고 함께 따라와라.
Lord Ieyasu!
이에야스 님!
Thank you!
감사합니다!
I wonder if the semi-final match is over.
이제 끝났을까, 준결승.
Please let Mr. Musashi be the winner.
무사시 씨가 이기도록...
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Mr. Musashi! The match shouldn't be already over!
무사시 씨! 아직 시합이!
We can't do that anymore-dasu.
그럴 때가 아니게 되었소.
Huh?
어?
That Hanzō is looking to steal the treasures of Jipangu State this time-dasu.
그 한조가 이번엔 지팡구국의 보물을 노리고 있소.
Because of that, I have to stay in the castle from this night and do a guard duty-dasu.
덕분에 나, 오늘밤부터 성에 묵으며 성 경비를 하게 되었소.
Then it means that we can't meet again.
그럼 다시 못 만나게 되는 거네.
Otsuru...
오츠루...
It'll be alright-dasu! That Edo Castle is within a stone's throw-dasu. I'll skip the guard duty and come see you-dasu!
괜찮소! 엎드리면 코 닿을 데의 에도 성이오. 경비 째고 종종 보러 오오!
That's right. I'll go everyday to give you dangos!
그렇네. 나도 매일 단고 보내러 갈게.
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Right! Let me make today's amount right away.
그래! 그럼 바로 오늘 분량 만들어 줄게.
Otsuru is so kind-dasu!
오츠루 정말 상냥하오!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨!
Are you okay, Mr. Musashi?
괜찮아? 무사시 씨!
What ultra fool threw a stone-dasu?!
누구이오! 돌 던진 바보멍청이는!
It was you, Osenchan...
아니, 센쨩.
Who's an ultra fool?
누가 바보멍청이야?
Nonononono... that's...
아니아니아니아니, 그게...
It's not the time to buy dangos! We have to go back to the castle as soon as possible!
단고 따위 사고 있을 때가 아니잖아? 한시라도 빨리 성에 돌아가야 하는데!
No-dasu! I'm here just to tell Otsuru that I can't come to meet her for a while-dasu!
아니오! 나 오츠루한테 잠시 못 만난다고 말하러 왔을 뿐이오!
Mr. Musashi, who's this?
무사시 씨, 이 사람은?
She's Osenchan whom I traveled with-dasu.
같이 여행한 오센짱이오.
You must be Otsuru. Musashi told me about you.
네가 오츠루구나. 무사시한테 들었어.
Traveled with?
같이 여행을?
I see. She's pretty.
그렇구나. 예쁜 분이네.
N- no, if you're going to say something that's true, then do it loudly!
아, 아니, 그런 사실을 말하려면 더 큰 목소리로 말해!
But her personality is bad-dasu.
그래도 성격 나쁘오.
What are you being stupid about?! Say that again!
뭔 개소리야! 다시 한번 말해봐라!
I get it! You're beautiful, Osenchan!
알겠소! 오센짱은 미인이오!
-And? -Beautiful, dead straight, has a good personality, rich,
-그리고? -미인에 똑바르고 성격 좋고 부자이고-
-Not yet! List more! -But!
-아직아직! 부족해! -그래도!
Hey, Otsuru!
어, 오츠루!
Otsuru! Dangos!
오츠루! 단고!
I don't care!
몰라!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
What happened-dasu?
대체 어떻게 된 것이오?
W- what's that?!
저, 저게 뭐야?!
A crisis is approaching Edotopia! Wait for the stormy latter half!
에도토피아에 위기가 다가온다! 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Mr. Ieyasu. Are they the strongest Karakuri martial artists that you chose?
이에야스 님. 이 자들이 말씀하신 최강의 카라쿠리 무예가입니까.
This glum man does look strong, but aren't the other two still children?
이 쪽의 떨떠름한 사내는 아무래도 강해 보이지만, 나머지 둘은 아직 아이 아닙니까.
You're one rude old man-dasu! We just went to the semi-finals of the martial arts contest-dasu!
실례하는 할배이오! 이래뵈도 우리는 무예 대회의 준결승까지 갔소!
Shut your mouth, Musashi! We're at the presence of the Highness!
말을 삼가라, 무사시! 국왕 전하의 어전이다!
But!
그래도!
These people fought against Hanzō and won for numerous times. Rest assured.
이 자들은 한조하고 몇 번이고 훌륭히 상대해 싸워 왔습니다. 안심하십시오.
Oh, is that so? If you do certify them...
아, 그렇습니까. 이에야스 님이 그렇게 말씀하신다면.
Anyway, your Highness, can we take a look at the targeted sacred sword?
어쨌든, 국왕 전하, 노림받는 성검을 삼가 볼 수 있습니까.
This is it.
이것이 그것입니다.
Other than this sword, there exist the round jewel and the sword.
이 검 외에도 곡옥과 방패가 있어, 그 셋을 가진 자가 이 지팡구국의 국왕이 됩니다.
Lord! We have a problem! Something giant that looks like a castle has appeared at Edotopia Bay!
영주님! 큰일입니다. 에도토피아 만에 거대한 성같은 것이 나타났습니다!
What?!
뭣이?!
A castle is walking towards here-dasu!
성이 걸어오오!
That Hanzō appeared with something so nonsensical!
한조 놈! 말도 안 되는 것을 가지고 나타났구나!
Informing to Ieyasu and the king. Hand over the sacred sword, or I'll crash this Megaton Castle to Edo Castle!
이에야스 및 국왕에게 알린다. 바로 성검을 넘겨라. 그러지 않으면 이 메가톤성을 에도 성에 부딪힌다!
That's different! That voice is not Hanzō's!
아니야! 저 목소리는 한조가 아니야!
Who are you-dasu?!
누구이오, 당신은?!
I am Dokuganryu, a family member of Rikudomaoh looking to rule over the world!
나는 이 세상을 지배하려는 육도마왕의 가신, 도쿠간류다!
Ieyasu, answer me right now. I am impatient.
자, 이에야스, 어서 대답해라. 나는 성미가 급하다.
You bastard! Everyone! Return the fire! We will not hand over the sacred sword!
네이놈! 다들 뭘 하나! 응전해라! 절대 성검을 넘길 수는 없다!
What kind of monster is that?!
뭔 괴물이냐.
Lord Ieyasu. It is dangerous here. You have to take shelter!
이에야스 님. 이대로는 위험합니다. 어서 피난을!
You fool! Do you think that the ruler of a country can flee from the castle?
멍청한 놈! 나라의 주인이 성에서 달아날 수 있을 것 같나!
Hey! Fire, fire, and keep firing!
이랴, 쏴라, 쏴라, 막 쏴라!
We'll end up becoming crushed at this rate!
아, 이대로는 찌부러지겠어!
If our castle can move too, it would be a good battle between two castles.
이쪽의 성도 움직일 수 있다면 성 대 성으로 좋은 경기가 가능할 텐데.
That's it-dasu, that's it-dasu! You can be right sometimes-dasu!
그거이오, 그거이오! 이야, 당신도 올바른 소리를 하오!
Hey, Musashi! What are you doing to the Highness?!
야, 무사시! 국왕 전하께 뭔 짓을!
We have one-dasu! The castle that will stand up to them!
있소, 우리에게도 놈들에게 지지 않을 성이!
Musashi, what do you mean by the castle that will stand up to Megaton Castle?
무사시, 메가톤성에 지지 않을 성이 어디 있다는 거냐?
That's it-dasu!
저것이오!
Fusion Castle! That does move!
오, 합체성이군. 저거라면 돌아다닐 수 있겠어.
This must be the cockpit of Fusion Castle!
와, 이게 합체성의 조종석이오!
Alright! We're moving forward-dasu!
좋소, 출발이오!
We'll crash this to the enemy and knock it over-dasu!
이걸 상대에게 부딪혀서 쓰러트려 주겠소!
My pointy nose...
내 높은 코가...
What was that for, Musashi?!
뭔 짓이야, 무사시!
Look at that-dasu!
저걸 보시오!
Damn!
이거!
We can't go through here-dasu. I thought I had a good idea...
아, 이대로는 못 지나가오. 기껏 좋은 아이디어라 생각했더니...
Don't give up, Musashi! This castle can divided into seven!
포기하지 마라, 무사시! 이 성은 7개로 분리할 수 있어!
But who'll move those 7 parts-dasu? There are only 3 here-dasu.
그래도 7개로 나뉘어도 누가 움직이오. 여기엔 3명밖에 없소.
That was unusually clever.
평소하고 다르게 현명한 소리를.
We'll help!
우리가 도웁시다!
Boss Zenigatan! Jiraiyan! Mr. Ushiwaka! Mr. Benkei in addition!
제니가탄 두목! 지라이얀! 우시와카 씨! 덤으로 벤케이 씨도!
I am not an addition!
난 덤이 아니다!
As a fellow martial artist, I cannot forgive an evil wrongdoing like that!
같은 무예가로서 저런 악한 잘못된 행위는 용서할 수 없습니다!
Me too! I'm really up for a real fight, since I've changed recently!
나도야! 최근 체질이 바뀌었더니 나쁜 놈들하고 싸울 생각에 근질근질하다!
Whoever disrupts the peace of Edotopia will not be forgiven by me, Zenigatan!
에도토피아의 평화를 어지럽히는 놈은 이 제니가탄이 가만둘 수는 없다!
Everyone! Alright! We'll show the friendship powers of Karakuri martial artists-dasu!
다들! 좋소! 카라쿠리 무예가의 우정 파워를 보여주겠소!
Alright, everyone! Let's go-dasu!
좋소, 다들! 가오!
Set out for Edo castle!
에도성을 향해 출발!
Right!
좋다!
It was big when it was far away, but it's even bigger when it got closer!
멀리서 봤는데도 큰데, 가까이서 보니 더욱이 크구나!
Mr. Ieyasu. We have to get the Highness to somewhere safe.
이에야스 님. 어서 국왕 전하를 안전한 곳으로.
No. If this Edo Castle gets destroyed, there is no more safe place.
아니, 이 에도 성이 부서지면 더이상 안전한 곳은 없습니다.
Musashi, Kojirō, hurry up and come!
아, 무사시, 코지로, 어서 와!
If you don't want to have your castle destroyed, then hand over the sacred sword!
자, 부서지고 싶지 않으면 순순히 성검을 넘겨라!
I refuse! No fool will acknowledge you bastards as the king of this country!
거절한다! 누가 네놈 따위를 이 나라의 왕으로 인정할 쏘냐!
Then die. We can always find the sacred sword later in peace.
그럼 죽어라. 성검은 다음에 여유롭게 찾아 주겠다.
We're doomed!
이제 틀렸어!
Stop-dasu!
기다리시오!
That must be Fusion Castle!
오, 합체성!
Musashi!
무사시!
We aren't afraid of Megaton Castle anymore, since we got this-dasu!
이제 이걸로 메가톤성 따위 무섭지 않소!
You fool! Do you really think that you can defeat Megaton Castle with something that small?!
멍청한 놈. 그런 쪼까만 걸로 메가톤성을 이길 수 있을 거라 생각하냐!
You can judge whether it's small after this-dasu!
쪼까만지 어떤지는 이걸 보고 말하시오!
T- that's!
이, 이건!
Hmph. Fusion Castle. You used your brain for once, Musashi.
흥, 합체성. 머리 좀 썼구나, 무사시.
Did you see-dasu? This is Fusion Castle, the ultimate stadium of Jipangu Martial Arts Competition-dasu!
보았소? 이 지팡구 무예 대회 궁극의 경기장, 합체성이오!
Here we go-dasu!
가오!
You bastard! How impudent of you!
에잇, 네이놈! 건방진 짓을!
Power room! Do you repeat? Power room!
동력실! 들리냐! 동력실!
This is the power room. To explain about how Megaton Castle moves,
여기가 동력실이다. 메가톤성이 어떻게 움직이는지 말하자면,
5 monks named The Five Mystery Monks move it with psychokinesis.
오괴승이라는 5명의 중이 염력으로 움직이고 있다.
Power room! Full power!
동력실! 풀 파워!
We don't lose-dasu!
지지 않소!
Everyone, power up-dasu!
다들 파워 업이오!
You're pretty good. But you won't evade this!
꽤 하는구나. 그러나 이건 못 피하겠지.
Musashi!
무사시!
Musashi! Are you okay, Musashi?!
무사시! 괜찮냐, 무사시?!
I'm fine-dasu.
괜찮소.
Now, while this holds up, let's sink them into the sea!
자, 이게 부서지지 않는 동안 놈들을 바다에 빠트려 버리자!
It's at its limit!
이제 한계다!
Let's escape!
탈출하자!
Hah! I knew that was children's toy! It can't possibly be an enemy of this Megaton Castle!
하! 결국 얘들 장난감. 이 메가톤성의 적이 아니다!
Now, crush Edo Castle at once!
자! 한번에 에도성을 깔아뭉개라!
Lord Dokuganryu!
도쿠간류 님!
What is it?!
뭐야?!
The power room isn't making any power!
동력실의 파워가 0이 되었습니다!
What?!
뭣이?!
You bastards... This will be paid back!
네이놈... 이 빚은 꼭 갚아 주겠다!
Emergency firecracker rocket, ignite!
비상용 로켓 불꽃 점화!
Hmph! We won-dasu!
흥이오! 우리 승리이오!
-Musashi! -Good job! Good job!
-무사시! -이야, 훌륭해, 훌륭해!
You did it, Musashi.
해냈구나, 무사시.
No, it's thanks to everyone-dasu.
아니, 모두의 덕분이오.
Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
Otsuru, you're safe-dasu!
오츠루, 무사했었소!
I was worried about you, Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨야말로 걱정했어, 나!
You must be hungry after that fighting!
싸워서 배고프지?
Have this!
자, 여기!
I'm so deeply happy-dasu! Dangos after a battle are the best-dasu!
우와, 감격이오! 전투 후의 단고는 제일 맛있소!
Osenchan!
오센짱!
You usual idiot did a great job today! You were hiding your brain capabilities!
계속 바보짓만 하던 놈이 오늘은 대활약이구나! 그 뇌의 능력을 숨기고 있었구나!
No, no, stop it-dasu! Stop it-dasu!
아니아니, 그만하시오! 그만하시오!
Now, Mr. Kojirō and everyone, you must be hungry! Have some dangos.
자, 코지로 씨하고 여러분, 배고프시죠? 단고 드세요.
Oh, right, thank you!
아, 예, 잘 먹겠습니다.
Yeah!
네!
My dangos!
아, 내 단고!
-Otsuru! -Hey, Musashi, smile! Smile!
-오츠루! -야, 무사시, 웃어, 웃어!
Otsuru!
오츠루!
That fearful Megaton Castle was beaten off by the friendship power of Musashi and his friends.
무서운 메가톤성은 무사시 일행의 우정 파워로 물리쳤다.
But Musashi got a new problem.
그러나 무사시 앞에는 새로운 문제가.
That was Otsuru who is very jealous.
그건 질투가 강한 오츠루였다.
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
That unmanageable person Osenchan's going to rescue the Highness who's really handsome,
꽤나 남자친구를 찾지 못한 난폭한 말과 같은 오센짱이, 무슨, 미남인 국왕 전하를 구하게 되고 말았소.
Megaton Castle came to attack again, and Edotopia's on big fire-dasu!
거기에 다시 메가톤성이 공격해 와서 에도토피아에 큰 화재이오!
Jiraiyan and others are doing their best to put off fire, but Otsuru's dango store is also burnt-dasu!
지라이얀 일행이 필사적으로 소화 작업을 하고 있지만 오츠루의 단고집이 불타버렸소!
Next story! Senhime's Love Wins
다음 이야기! 센히메의 사랑은 이기오
It's a stormy cooked dango-dasu!
질풍노도의 구운 단고오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
Senhime's Love
센히메의 사랑은
Wins
이기오
Look forwards for it!
기대하세요!